Pablo Francisco Zambrano Moncayo

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pablo-zambrano/ Mobile: +61 450 726 664 Email: pfzm@hotmail.com

I have over 5 years experience working in the Hospitality and Tourism industry in a diverse range of positions. I have acquired a number of skills from my work experience and different disciplines including leadership, innovation, creativity, teamwork and problem solving. I am looking to move forward in my career to a role where I am able to utilise my skill set in an environment of continuing to learn, to achieve beneficial outcomes for all the stakeholders in the company I work for.

Work Experience:

Hyatt Hotel Corporation – Global Contact Center Pacific Business Leader Distribution Services, Learning, Development and Customer Service. August 2019 – Present

- Manage Distribution Services (Data Services) team for South East Asia and Pacific region for Hyatt hotels. Our team is in charge of rate loading on Hyatt booking channels, OTAs and GDS (Sabre, Worldspan, Apollo/Galileo, Amadeus). Troubleshooting any issues with Hyatt booking channels.
- ➤ Part of the Hyatt Global Build team. In charge of new hotel builds in the South East Asia and Pacific region on Hyatt booking systems and set up the connectivity with Hyatt partners.
- Member of the Hyatt Global Learning and Development team. In this team with the leaders around the globe we plan strategies and organize projects to implement across the Hyatt Global Contact Centres.
- > Planning and training all new staff members of the Hyatt Global Contact Centre Pacific.
- ➤ Training and development of all the Hyatt Global Contact Centre Pacific in new skills: Loyalty Program Specialist, Guest Care Advocates, Social Care Advocates (Social Media customer service).
- > Supervising operations and the team (19 staff members) of the Hyatt Global Contact Center Pacific to ensure guest satisfaction and safety according to Hyatt International Standards and making sure KPIs are met.
- ➤ Handling and resolving guest's escalations concerning quality and service through diverse channels such as: Social Media, Hyatt Guest Support platform and voice channels.

Hyatt Hotel Corporation – Global Contact Center Pacific Reservation Sales Associate July 2016 – August 2019

- ➤ Handling and resolving guests enquires and escalations through diverse channels as Social Media, Hyatt Guest Support platform, emails and voice channels.
- > Supervising operations of the Global Contact Center Pacific during evening hours and weekend shifts.
- Ensuring and assisting in loading corporate rates, special promotions and any updates in Hyatt reservation's system, website and GDS (Global Distribution System).
- Making sure Hyatt Australian properties get the correct compensation for Loyalty Program (World Of Hyatt) Free Nights/ Upgrades Awards according to Comp Values and Occupancy for each property and assisting when is needed with other Hyatt International Teams.

The Westin Melbourne Service Express Agent July 2014 – August 2016

Achievements: Outstanding Brand Champion "Caring for Associates" for the 1st Quarter of 2015.

- Ensuring that guests, both internal and external, are provided with a prompt, personal service that in instinctive and ensures their needs are met.
- Answering any guest's requests and dispatching them to the allocated operational department.
- Following up to ensure that all guests requests are completed in a timely manner.
- Resolving any issues for unsatisfied guests and follow through until resolution.

Handcraft Brewery "Cerveceria La Caleruna SAS Sales and Marketing November 2011 – July 2013

Sahilu SAS Event coordinator October 2011 – July 2012

Amaranto Cafe-Bar Chef July 2010 – November 2010

Volunteering:

St Vincent de Paul Society – Melbourne, Australia
Volunteer at Soup Vans Program
2017 - 2019

Education and Qualifications:

Bachelor's Degree of Tourism and Hospitality Management, William Angliss Institute,
Melbourne - Australia
Technologist in Gastronomy and Restaurant Management (Advanced Diploma), Fundación
Tecnológica Liderazgo Canadience Internacional – LCI Bogotá - Colombia
Gestalt Theraphy Trainning – Centro Gestalt de la Sabana, Bogotá - Colombia
Barista Development, Escuela Colombiana de Café, Bogotá – Colombia
Concept and Vision in Buisness Development of Coffee Shops, Escuela Colombiana de Café
Bogotá – Colombia

Languages:

Fluent in Spanish and English

Work references available upon request